<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-07-09T15:03:47+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">2late2nate</title><subtitle>Welcome to my website. I&apos;ll be hosting all of my blogposts and professional work here. Enjoy your stay.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">first post, first step</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2025/07/02/first-post.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="first post, first step" /><published>2025-07-02T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2025-07-02T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2025/07/02/first-post</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2025/07/02/first-post.html"><![CDATA[<p><strong>Hello world!</strong> Or whatever it is that computers say.</p>

<p>I am currently typing this post in VSCode, right after a few days of wrestling with my terminal and Jekyll itself to get it to finally work… And I’m not very experienced with using my terminal nor Jekyll just yet, so you can imagine how torturous the entire process was. I did manage to learn a lot of things though. I have no regrets when it comes to that.</p>

<p>I’m already decently experienced in HTML and CSS, so setting up the code for that was no problem. When it came to Liquid and linking all these pages together using something other than relative and absolute links, however, I had a lot of problems. But, with the help of the Jekyll docs, I was able to make something that just <em>barely</em> functioned. Hell yeah.</p>

<p>I don’t have much else to say, really.. All I plan to use this blog for is to document my journey in learning new programming languages, the development of this site itself, and other things I deem professional or formal enough to be placed here, instead of any of my social media pages. I’ll end this blogpost with a quick to-do list for this website, and I’ll be signing off. I might make that a habit for all of my blogposts, actually.</p>

<hr />

<p><strong>Projects</strong></p>
<ul>
  <li><strong>Work on Github Pages site</strong>
    <ul>
      <li><del>Figure out how Jekyll works..!</del></li>
      <li><del>Create index page</del></li>
      <li><del>Create about page</del></li>
      <li>Create portfolio page</li>
      <li>Create credits page</li>
      <li>Make site responsive</li>
    </ul>
  </li>
</ul>

<hr />

<p>That’s it for my first post. Thanks for reading.</p>]]></content><author><name>Nate</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello world! Or whatever it is that computers say.]]></summary></entry></feed>